And as you see, this is what we have, you know?
So I can upload more images and add up to my layers
over here as you see.
And what else can I do?
I can come here and use the AI tools
that the photo editor provides me with, right?
So first let me to click on this close button.
Yes.
So over here, as you see, we can tap in hands.
We can use AI upscaler.
We can use the magic eraser.
So what will it do?
It will erase an object, probably, right?
We can use the background remover.
We can use the face ombler error, you know?
We can use the AI skin retouch.
So this is for the retouching.
So for example, let's try it out on this very image
that I have over here.
So yep, this is it.
I upload it.
And for example, I want to do skin retouching on it, right?
So this is my image I selected.
And then I click on AI skin retouch and wait.
So it says upgrade with 30% off.
Nope, thanks.
I don't want that.
But did it happen or not?
OK, it's probably going to be a premium option
if it's not working.
But whatever.
Yes, so I close this.